JACKSON McCARTHY

WEB DEVELOPER

EDUCATION

DIPLOMA/CREDITS -

2009-2013

UHSSE - UHART SCHOOL OF SCIENCE & ENGINEERING -

HARTFORD CT, USA "Early college high school located on the campus of University of Hartford" I spent 2 semesters at UHart in 2013 studying MVCalculus before transferring to UCONN.

UCONN - 2014 - 2017 UNIVERSITY OF CONNECTICUT-

STORRES AND HARTFORD, USA Major studies in mathematics, PHYSICS, PHILOSOPHY. AFTER 4 YEARS TRANSFERRED TO CLOSE OUT A DEGREE AND TRANSITION INTO WEB-DEVELOPMENT

ASSOCIATE OF SCIENCE -

TUNXIS- CONNECTICUT, USA

SKILLS

REASONING & PROBLEM SOLVING

ADAPTABILITY

ATTENTION TO DETAIL

MATHEMATICS

WEB DEVELOPMENT

LEADERSHIP AND MANAGEMENT

PROFILE

I am a newly certified full-stack web developer with a long dedication to the pursuit of science and mathematics, balanced as well with the study of philosophy and art. I am a skilled trade laborer and plasterer with a decade of experience working both in the field and in jobsite management. I am a motivated worker and experienced project manager that collaborates well with others.

EXPERIENCE

LABORER/MATERIAL-COORDINATOR - DEC. 2012 - 2021

ARTISAN PLASTER & RESTORATION - New Britain, CT, USA

I began in this field as a general laborer working my way up to a skilled labor employee while apprenticing in plastering. Working full-time while I went to college I coordinated material requirements and delivery to job sites as well as preparing the sites for the work to come.

Major accomplishments:

- Taught me invaluable skills for working efficiently in teams
- Provided me with the work ethic to grind everyday for a company I respect

WEB DEV EDUCATION - 2021 - 2022

UCONN SCHOOL OF ENGINEERING CODING BOOTCAMP - Full-stack web-dev course. This school curricula boasts the most in-demand market skills needed for a career in web-development.

Major accomplishments:

- Graduated this course with honors
- Assisted other classmates with the formation of an interactive study group to help others achieve success in this course as well

INTERESTS







SCIENCE





PHILOSOPHY